let questions5 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to acquaint",
      answer: "C. sich vertraut machen",
      options: [
        "A. vergessen",
        "B. ignorieren",
        "C. sich vertraut machen",
        "D. entfernen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "cemetery",
      answer: "A. Friedhof",
      options: [
        "A. Friedhof",
        "B. Park",
        "C. Garten",
        "D. Kirche"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to curse",
      answer: "D. verfluchen",
      options: [
        "A. segnen",
        "B. bewundern",
        "C. begrüßen",
        "D. verfluchen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "disguise",
      answer: "B. Verkleidung",
      options: [
        "A. Kleidung",
        "B. Verkleidung",
        "C. Rüstung",
        "D. Maske"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "fancy",
      answer: "A. schick",
      options: [
        "A. schick",
        "B. einfach",
        "C. altmodisch",
        "D. schmutzig"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "flashlight",
      answer: "C. Taschenlampe",
      options: [
        "A. Kerze",
        "B. Laterne",
        "C. Taschenlampe",
        "D. Glühbirne"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "hood",
      answer: "D. Kapuze",
      options: [
        "A. Hut",
        "B. Schal",
        "C. Mütze",
        "D. Kapuze"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "inhabitant",
      answer: "B. Einwohner",
      options: [
        "A. Besucher",
        "B. Einwohner",
        "C. Reisender",
        "D. Fremder"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to nourish",
      answer: "C. ernähren",
      options: [
        "A. hungern",
        "B. vernachlässigen",
        "C. ernähren",
        "D. vergessen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "pirate",
      answer: "A. Pirat",
      options: [
        "A. Pirat",
        "B. Matrose",
        "C. Händler",
        "D. Kapitän"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "publication",
      answer: "B. Veröffentlichung",
      options: [
        "A. Manuskript",
        "B. Veröffentlichung",
        "C. Artikel",
        "D. Skizze"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "riddle",
      answer: "C. Rätsel",
      options: [
        "A. Frage",
        "B. Witz",
        "C. Rätsel",
        "D. Aufgabe"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "to rot",
      answer: "A. verrotten",
      options: [
        "A. verrotten",
        "B. wachsen",
        "C. gedeihen",
        "D. trocknen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to scare",
      answer: "D. erschrecken",
      options: [
        "A. beruhigen",
        "B. erfreuen",
        "C. langweilen",
        "D. erschrecken"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "shortly",
      answer: "C. bald",
      options: [
        "A. später",
        "B. niemals",
        "C. bald",
        "D. selten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "skeleton",
      answer: "B. Skelett",
      options: [
        "A. Knochen",
        "B. Skelett",
        "C. Körper",
        "D. Statue"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to spoil",
      answer: "A. verderben",
      options: [
        "A. verderben",
        "B. bewahren",
        "C. verbessern",
        "D. retten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to starve",
      answer: "D. hungern",
      options: [
        "A. essen",
        "B. genießen",
        "C. wachsen",
        "D. hungern"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "thrill",
      answer: "C. Nervenkitzel",
      options: [
        "A. Langeweile",
        "B. Angst",
        "C. Nervenkitzel",
        "D. Ruhe"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "wicked",
      answer: "D. böse",
      options: [
        "A. gut",
        "B. freundlich",
        "C. gerecht",
        "D. böse"
      ]
    }
  ];
  export default questions5;
  